CHARLES ADAMTEY



CONTACT

Tema, Ghana AC14212 Mobile: +233558595238 charliegrid123@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH: December 12 1992

MARRIAGE STATUS: in relationship

NATIONALITY: Ghanian

EDUCATION

March 2013 Hn.D:Hardware, Software And Networking, Engineerfing IPMC, Accra

July 2012 High School Diploma Oyoko Methodist Snr High Sch, Koforidua

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Determined commis chef promoting great stamina, passion and versatility. flexible individual skilled working as part of busy team and interested in helping in different task. Over five years of experience in busy, high-end restaurant environments.

Ambitious individual promoting a strong understanding of the food and beverage industry. Knowledgeable in food stuck rotation and kitchen safety collaborative individual trained and ready to succeed in high-volume food environment. Offering exemplary stuck rotation inventory oversight skills. Ready to master new challenges in the role of commis chef. Eager commis chef interested in learning and ready to tackle any kitchen task. Emerging professional with drive to work hard and be successful. Reliable employee seeking commis chef position and offering excellent communication and good judgement.

SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Quality Assesment
- Team Collabration
- Data Analysis

- Relationship Building Creative Thinking
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Performance improvement
- Time Management

HOBBIES

- Cooking
- Reading
- Drawing
- listening to music
- workout
- Sports

WORK HISTORY

January 2014-March 2015

IT Technician. Mec IT, Tema, Ghana

- Troubleshooting and diagnosing computer hardware and software issues
- Setting up computer networking systems
- Assisting employees and customers with IT-related problems

May 2015-January 2016 Interior Designer, Pro painting services, Accra, Ghana

- House painting
- Residential interior and exterior
- wallpaper installations
- painting and designs
- •Art works
- wall skimming

March 2016 - December 2018

Commis chef, Mensvic Grand Hotel, Accra, East Legon, Ghana

- Assisting in the food preparation process
- Cooking and preparing elements of high quality dishes
- Preparing vegetables and restocking
- Assisting with stock rotation and cleaning stations
- Contribution to maintaining Kitchen and food safety standards.

January 2019 - March 2021

Commis Chef Oak Plaza Hotel, spintex Road, East Airport,

- Manage food preparation activities, such as cutting ingredient to size and preparing sauces and garnishes.
- Maintained cleanliness and order of kitchen prep areas and appliances as well as convenient organization of ingredients.
- Floated through out Kitchen to assist in meal preparation and plating, effectively.
- Washed, peeled and cut various food such fruits and vegetables to prepare for cooking or serving.